lloydslist.com 2017-06-13

# Lloyd's List - Privacy policy

**Confidentiality**

The parties acknowledge and confirm that during the term of this Agreement and following its termination the parties shall treat as confidential and shall not (other than in the proper provision of the Service or as required by applicable law) use or disclose to any person, firm or company, terms of this Agreement and any confidential information relating to the business of and belonging to the other party, nor permit its use or disclosure. This obligation of confidentiality shall not apply to information that is publicly known (through no fault of the non-disclosing party) or not of commercial value to such other party.

 **Access to other web sites**

You may be able to access other sites via links from the Web Site. These sites are not under our control and we are not responsible in any way for any of their contents. We make no representations whatsoever about any other web sites that you may access through the Web Site or which may link to our Web Site. Any concerns regarding any external link should be directed to its web site administrator or web master.

 **Third party material on the Web Site**

You may see advertising material submitted by third parties on the Web Site. Individual advertisers are solely responsible for the content of advertising material that they submit to us, including ensuring that it complies with relevant legislation. We accept no responsibility for the content of advertising material, including, without limitation, any error, omission or inaccuracy therein. If you would like to advertise on the Web Site, please send an email to: marketing@lloydslist.com.

 **What Information Do We Collect?**

We collect the domain name and e-mail address (where possible) of visitors to our Web page, the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, user-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit and information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information, and/or site registrations. When you undertake to request a count on this site we ask for your name, e-mail address, company name, address, post code, phone number, job title, industry, and business interests. Once you have registered a count with us and signed up to our services (paid or otherwise), you are not anonymous to us. In order to tailor our subsequent communications to you and continuously improve our products and services, we may also ask you to provide us with information regarding your professional interests, experience with our products, and more detailed contact preferences.

 **Use of Personal Information**

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web page, to notify consumers about updates to our Web site, and may be compiled and shared with other companies within the Informa Group to contact consumers for marketing purposes. It may also be shared with reputable third party organisations to help them contact consumers for marketing purposes.

 **Use of Cookies**

A cookie is a small text file written to a user's hard drive that contains the User ID. The cookies do not contain any personal information about users and in themselves only record those areas of the site that have been visited by the computer in question, and for how long. The use of cookies is now widespread by sites in order to track traffic flows. We use cookies to enable us to offer certain time-saving features to our users such as, one-time log in, global-site shopping cart functionality and pre-populating name and address fields. If a user sets up his browser to reject the cookie, he or she may still use the site although functionality will be impaired. You can find out more about the use of cookies at: www.cookiecentral.com.

 **Log Files**

We use cookies and log files to administer the site, track users' movements and actions, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. The information gathered can thus be used to improve the site and the user experience.

 **Data protection**

The following applies to any information you provide to us, for example during any registration or ordering or confirmation of details process; 1. You authorise us to use, store or otherwise process any personal information which relates to and identifies you, including but not limited to your name and address, to the extent reasonably necessary to provide the Services which are available through our Web Site by us or our sub-contractors. Unless you have indicated on the registration form that you do not wish to receive direct marketing material, your personal details will be included on a database compiled for direct marketing purposes. From time to time you may receive direct marketing information, either from us or from third parties. All such information collected by us shall be referred to in these Terms and Conditions as "Personal Information". You must ensure that the Personal Information you provide is accurate and complete and that all ordering or contact details contain your correct name, e-mail address and other requested details;2. You acknowledge and agree to be bound by the terms of our Privacy Statement. By accepting the Agreement, you agree to the processing and disclosure of the Personal Information for the provision of the Services and supply of the Products. If you would like to review or modify any part of your Personal Information or you have not indicated that you do not wish to receive direct marketing material, but change your mind about this you should notify Customer Services at database@informa.com. As soon after this as is reasonably practicable, we will remove your name from the direct marketing database. We reserve the right to charge a statutory administration fee to deal with any request from you for access to the Personal Information.
